

# MITHILA SWANSI

**UX** Designer

# Contact

**Address** 

Tokyo, Japan 136-0072

**Phone** 

+819033132299

E-mail

sutarmithila@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/mithila-sutar

**WWW** 

https://sutarmithila.medium.com

#### **Skills**

**UX** architecture

Wireframing and Prototype Design

Design thinking and Visual design

User Research

Adobe Creative Suite

Mobile Design UX Design

Senior UX designer with 7.4 years experience and specialization in complex web application design. Achieved 15% increase in user satisfaction and 20% increase in conversions through the creation of interactively tested, data-driven, and user-centered design.

# **Work History**

2021-08 -2023-08

#### SR. UX DESIGNER

Accenture, Pune

- Track and Trace: Gather client requirements,
  Created visual design prototypes, designed
  icons, and developed solutions for a new
  navigation system, resulting in a 10% increase in
  user satisfaction
- Worked on clients' feedback, and suggested and improved user experience.
- Created interactive presentation for PI demo
- Presented UX designs and solutions to senior staff, evangelizing for user-centric design decisions.
- Researched and proposed new solutions to make website more user-friendly.
- Customer Engagement Platform: Suggesting and improving old wireframes with more user-friendly designs
- Gather client requirements, Worked on wireframing, Make it functional by prototyping the wireframing using Figma and Adobe XD.
- Achieved higher conversion rates with carefully crafted UI elements that align with brand guidelines while also meeting user expectations.
- Optimized navigation structures based on user feedback analysis resulting in reduced bounce rates on various web pages.
- Implemented strategies to increase web site traffic.

2019-11 -2021-05

#### SR. UX DESIGNER

Clodura System pvt Itd, Pune

- Design 'RADAR' software which builds client relationship data.
- Developed user personas with scenarios to improve functionality and usability for target audience contributing to 15% increase in conversions.

Responsive design

#### Software

Figma

Upper intermediate

**Photoshop** 

Upper intermediate

Adobe XD

Upper intermediate

Canva

Upper intermediate

Illustrator

Intermediate

# Languages

English

Bilingual or Proficient (C2)

Hindi

C2

Proficient

Marathi

Bilingual or Proficient (C2)

- Contributed to creating an online community with a UX modeled after industry-leading community sites, combining social proof with e-commerce conversion.
- Integrated social media, marketing content, e-commerce to fully implement monetized services throughout.
- Designed user experience for a revamped user "dashboard," increasing user satisfaction and contributing to average Trust Pilot review score increasing from 4.5 to 4.9.

2018-06 -2019-11

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

Rewise analytics and Technology

- Designed several E-book for client UK, US
- Design Social media posts, Banners, Infographics, and Business Cards designs using Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign
- Implemented brand guidelines across all designs, ensuring consistent look-and-feel throughout marketing efforts.

2016-05 -2018-06

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

Buzzle Software pvt Itd

- Develop and implement solutions for the Buzzle Software web application
- Involved in the complete software development lifecycle, including working with the production operations team to prepare and execute releases.

# **Education**

2011-01 -	BE COMPUTER SCIENCE
2015-12	Bharthi Vidyapeeth College of Engineering
2009-01 -	HSC
2011-12	Rajaram collage Science
2009-01	SSC

D.B.R.K.High School

# Awards

- Rising star Rewise Analytics and Technology.
- Winner of "Rangoli competition"